ogilvypr.com 2007-12-10

# Ogilvy Public Relations WorldwideOgilvy PR Worldwide: Privacy Policy

We respect the privacy of all individuals and our Privacy Policy is in place to help protect that privacy. This policy addresses activities from our servers. Other sites may have their own policies, which we do not control, and thus are not addressed or controlled by this policy.

**What Organization is Collecting the Information**  
Ogilvy Public Relations Worldwide is a global marketing communications firm, with offices in more than 60 cities around the world. Entering its 24th year providing public relations solutions, Ogilvy Public Relations Worldwide has specialties in consumer marketing, corporate (B2B), health & medical, technology, public affairs, social marketing and entertainment.

**Personal Information**  
We do not collect any personal information about you when you visit our Web site (other than the standard information automatically collected and stored in the Web logs) unless you choose to provide it to us.

Specifically, we collect information when you subscribe to our e-mail newsletter, send an e-mail to us, send us feedback, etc. When you e-mail a page, your e-mail addresses, and that of your recipient, are used only in the case of transmission errors. The information will not be used for any other purpose.

Ogilvy PR will not share any information collected with a third party. We do not sell your e-mail address, your name, or personal demographic information to any mass marketers or any other organizations.

Cookies (a message given to a Web browser by a Web server) are not used on this site.

**Information Collected by Server Logs**  
If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the Web site, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally.

We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit:

•  |  Your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address. (An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you go on the Web.)  
---|---  
•  |  The domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account).  
•  |  The Internet address of the Web site, if any, from which you came to our site.  
•  |  The date and time you arrived at our site and how long you spent visiting the site.  
•  |  The name and version of your computer's operating system and browser: for example, Windows 98/Netscape Navigator 5 (this information is supplied automatically by your computer).  
•  |  The pages you visit.   
  
We use this information to help us make the site more useful to visitors — to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. Unless it is specifically stated otherwise, no additional information will be collected about you.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Web site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

Back to Top
